<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PersolinoRoseGarden</string>
    <string name="benvenuti">Welcome</string>
    <string name="start">START YOUR VISIT</string>
    <string name="visitor">Visitor</string>
    <string name="technical">Techical</string>
    <string name="map">Map of the rose garden</string>
    <string name="elenco_rose">LIST OF ROSES</string>
    <string name="exit_button">If you have finished your visit click here</string>
    <string name="uscita">THANK YOU FOR</string>
    <string name="uscita2">YOUR VISIT</string>
    <string name="rosa1">CENTIFOLIA ROSE</string>
    <string name="descrizione1"> The Centifolia rose is called the rose of painters because it is often depicted in the paintings of Flemish artists. Developed in the Netherlands, its petals are bright pink, with bristly and green leaves and many thin thorns. </string>
    <string name="rosa2">TEA ROSE</string>
    <string name="descrizione2">The tea rose is called such because it is characterized by an intense aroma that recalls fresh tea. Originally from China, she traveled on ships used to transport tea to Europe. Characterized by bright yellow petals, it can reach a height of 2 meters. It produces fruits that are called achenes slightly covered by down. It can withstand both high and low temperatures but needs a lot of light to live.</string>
    <string name="tutte_rose">LOOK FOR ROSES</string>
    <string name="rosa3">ROSA MISTER LINCOLN</string>
    <string name="descrizione3">The Mister Lincoln rose blooms during the months in the summer and autumn months with a unique flowering. It has a scarlet red tone and is velvety to the touch. It is a double flower with 15 to 30 petals and an intense aroma. It can survive between -10 ° C and 37 ° C and is therefore suitable for habitats such as Northern Italy and the Apennines.</string>
    <string name="rosa4">ROSA GALLICA VERSICOLOR</string>
    <string name="descrizione4">This very ancient rose is a mutation of R. gallica officinalis. It is probably the oldest of the variegated roses. The flowers are light red and white, streaked in different ways. This plant does not develop particularly, it has a slightly erect and compact habit that changes, arching, when the flowering is at its maximum growth and is covered with light green leaves that fade to gray. It is not very thorny but the branches, twigs and peduncles are covered by a dense weave of bristles.
The most romantic of the many legends about it says that it takes its name from "Fair Rosamund", the lover of Henry II.
</string>

    <string name="fioritura">FLOWERING PERIOD</string>
    <string name="colore">COLOR</string>
    <string name="forma">SHAPE</string>
    <string name="profumo">PERFUME</string>
    <string name="area">CLIMATE AREA</string>
    <string name="altezza">HEIGHT</string>
    <string name="diametro">DIAMETER</string>
    <string name="malattie">ILLNESSES</string>

    <string name="fioritura1">Unique and Late</string>
    <string name="colore1">Pastel rose</string>
    <string name="forma1">Globulose, the flowers open in a deep cup</string>
    <string name="profumo1">Intoxicating and sweet </string>
    <string name="area1">All</string>
    <string name="altezza1">120</string>
    <string name="diametro1">10</string>
    <string name="malattie1">Mushrooms and parasites</string>

    <string name="fioritura2">May to September</string>
    <string name="colore2">Bright yellow</string>
    <string name="forma2">Large flowers consisting of the chalice consisting of 5 sepals and the corolla with 5 petals and stamas </string>
    <string name="profumo2">tea</string>
    <string name="area2"> Can withstand both high and low temperatures </string>
    <string name="altezza2">200</string>
    <string name="diametro2">9</string>
    <string name="malattie2">Mushrooms and parasites</string>

    <string name="fioritura3">June-October</string>
    <string name="colore3">velvety redscarlatto</string>
    <string name="forma3">Double flower with 15/30 petals</string>
    <string name="profumo3">intense</string>
    <string name="area3">survives between -10 and 37 degrees, in the north and in the Apennines</string>
    <string name="altezza3">100</string>
    <string name="diametro3">12</string>
    <string name="malattie3">mites and afidi</string>

    <string name="fioritura4">unique summer</string>
    <string name="colore4">Varied</string>
    <string name="forma4">Double semi with 22/34 petals </string>
    <string name="profumo4">great </string>
    <string name="area4">4/8 cold zones</string>
    <string name="altezza4">90</string>
    <string name="diametro4">90</string>
    <string name="malattie4">oidio</string>

    <string name="info">For more information</string>
    <string name="call">Chiamaci</string>
    <string name="credit">Created by: Angeli Luca, Gamberini Giulia, Raimondi Ilaria, Tarozzi Alessia</string>
    <string name="where">Ingegneria Elettronica e Telecomunicazioni - Università degli studi di Bologna - Laboratorio di Software per le telecomunicaioni</string>
</resources>